unos.org 2009-06-19

# United Network for Organ Sharing: Organ Donation and Transplantation

United Network for Organ Sharing (UNOS) understands how important the privacy of personal information is to our users. This notice describes UNOS' Privacy Policy as it relates to your use of [www.unos.org](http://www.unos.org/), <http://optn.transplant.hrsa.gov/>, [www.transplantliving.org](http://www.transplantliving.org/) and [www.donormemorial.org](http://www.donormemorial.org/) (collectively, "the Web site"). By visiting the Web site, you are accepting the policies described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you are not permitted to use the Web site. This Privacy Policy is inapplicable to information that you may send to UNOS by e-mail or other means of communication.

UNOS may periodically revise this policy. Your continued use of this Web site after changes have been posted will constitute your acceptance of such changes. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please use this form or contact us at:

United Network for Organ Sharing  
P.O. Box 2484   
Richmond, Virginia 23218

We are available to answer your questions and hear your concerns. 

UNOS may ask for and collect from you personally identifiable information at various points throughout the site. Depending on the information and/or services you request, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail address, address, phone number, payment details and similar information. Once you provide your personal information, you are not anonymous to UNOS. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it to us. 

When you do provide us with personal data, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: 

  * we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our services
  * we (or another government contractor) may use that information to contact you
  * we may provide other third parties with aggregate--but not individual--information about visitors to or users of our Web site 

We do not now and do not intend to sell, rent, or market personal data about you to third parties.  
If you choose to provide your credit card information to UNOS, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was provided. In addition, the companies we work with to process credit card transactions use high grade encryption and security protocols. 

In addition to the information gathered as described above, we may automatically collect non-personal technical information by using a technology called "cookies" when you connect to our Web site. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site. This information is collected to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data to facilitate content improvements.   
Revised August 11, 2008.
